AMIRPASHA MANIYAR

SOFT WARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+ 91 - 77 98 66 5559

Amirpasha.Maniyar@cognizant.com

PROFILE

9 years of professional experience in software development with agile scrum methodology. I have worked extensively with ASP.NET MVC, .Net Core, Angular, Web API Core, LINQ, Entity Framework, MS SQL Server, etc. Also having Work experience in workflow-based application (EdorasOne) and CMS oriented tools (Kentico and Sitefinity). I'm seeking a full-time position in the field of information technology.

TECHNOLOGIES

- C.#
- ASP.NET MVC 4 /5
- Angular 2 /5 /7 /9 /14/ 16
- Web API Core 2 /3
- LINQ
- Entity Framework
- MS SQL Server
- WCF
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- AJAX
- HTML5, CSS3
- JSON, XML
- EdorasOne
- Kentico 8.2, Sitefinity 7
- RabbitMQ, ElasticSearch
- Kibana, TeamCity, OCP
- Github, TFS and SVN
- Azure
- SonarQube

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

COGNIZANT | PUNE | OCT 2023 - Present

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

FIS | PUNE | SEP 2020 - OCT 2023

TECHNOLOGY ANALYST

INFOSYS | PUNE | NOV 2018 - SEP 2020

ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE

CYGNET | PUNE | JUL 2018 - NOV 2018

ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE

SYNECHRON | PUNE | APR 2015 - APR 2018

PROJECTS

APT | COGNIZANT

Role: Senior Software Engineer

Environment: Azure, Web API Core 6, Microservices, Angular 16, Visual Studio 2022, etc.

CLO | FIS

Role: Senior Software Engineer

Environment: Web API Core 3, Microservices, Angular 14, Visual Studio 2022, SQL Server 2019, etc.

XPO LOGISTICS | INFOSYS

Role: Technology Analyst

Environment: C#.Net, Web API Core 3, Microservices, Angular 9, Visual Studio 2019, Visual Studio Code, SQL Server 2019, etc.

SURVEY MONKEY | CYGNET

Role: Associate Software

Environment: C#.Net, Web API Core 2, LINQ, Entity Framework, Microservices, Angular 5, Visual Studio 2017, Visual Studio Code, SQL Server, Cloud (AWS), etc.

OSN TV | SYNECHRON

Role: Associate Software

Environment: ASP.NET, ASP.NET MVC 4, WCF, Kentico 8.2, SQL Server 2012 R2, VS2015, IIS 7.0, etc.

TULLOW OIL | SYNECHRON

Role: Junior Developer

Environment: ASP.NET MVC 4, LINQ, Entity Framework, Sitefinity 7, SQL Server 2013 R2, VS2015, IIS 7.0, etc.

EDUCATION

MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATION (MCA)

PUNE UNIVERSITY | AGGREGATE: 65.40

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS (BCA)

SRTMUN UNIVERSITY | AGGREGATE: 69.56

HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATE

LATUR BOARD | PERCENTAGE: 69.50

SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE

LATUR BOARD | PERCENTAGE: 61.20